<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ajpierce</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ajpierce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 11:36:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interacting with the Ethereum Blockchain in Clojure</title>
      <link>/posts/ethereum-blockchain-clojure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 11:36:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ethereum-blockchain-clojure/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the Ethereum blockchain has been the subject of much interest, driven in part by the huge success of CryptoKitties. Unfortunately for those of us hoping to perform kitty market analysis using our favorite language, there isn&amp;rsquo;t any good information for how to interact with the Ethereum Blockchain in Clojure. This blog post aims to get you up and running talking to the Ethereum Blockchain.
Prerequisites This post assumes you have a Geth node running locally on the default port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClojureScript: NPM in Figwheel in 60 Seconds</title>
      <link>/posts/react-figwheel-npm-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 17:11:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/react-figwheel-npm-2/</guid>
      <description>Update 2017-08-22 Looks like the latest version of Clojurescript (1.9.908) broke something! If you see an error that looks like this:
&amp;hellip;then you&amp;rsquo;ll have to downgrade Clojurescript to version 1.9.854. In the :dependencies block near the top of your project.clj, modify the Clojurescript version to look like:
[org.clojure/clojurescript &amp;quot;1.9.854&amp;quot;]  After that, restart figwheel and you should be good to go!
Thanks to Gene Kim for pointing this out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React in Figwheel from Scratch</title>
      <link>/posts/react-figwheel-npm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 15:58:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/react-figwheel-npm/</guid>
      <description>Update 2: 2017-08-10 This tutorial is out of date! Check out the updated version!
Update: 2017-07-30 Since publishing the original post, the Clojurescript team implemented CLJS-2280, which handles the work of shimming process.env for us.
As if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough, the team also released Clojurescript 1.9.854, meaning that we no longer need to build the latest version of Clojurescript from source!
The other thing that changed is that :npm-deps are no longer installed automatically, and the newly-added :install-deps build property is not yet supported in lein-figwheel, so I&amp;rsquo;m holding off on updating the tutorial until Figwheel catches up for us 👍</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>